Track 5.4 Mid-year review
Bài 5.4 Ôn tập giữa năm
Activity 3
Bài tập 3
Listen and tick or cross
Nghe và đánh dấu tích hoặc gạch chéo
Did you go to the swimming pool yesterday, Alf?
Hôm qua bạn có đi hồ bơi không, Alf?
No, I didn't. I helped my grandma with some chores.
Không. Mình giúp bà làm việc nhà.
Me too. I always help my grandma at the weekend.
Mình cũng vậy. Mình luôn giúp bà vào cuối tuần.
Did you go to the park at the weekend, Joan?
Cuối tuần bạn có đi công viên không, Joan?
Yes, I did. It was sunny and warm.
Có. Trời nắng và ấm.
Did you go to the park?
Bạn có đi công viên không?
Yes, I did.
Có.
Did you travel to school by bus this morning, Alf?
Sáng nay bạn có đi xe buýt đến trường không, Alf?
Yes, I did. Did you travel by bus?
Có. Bạn có đi xe buýt không?
No, I didn't. I walked with my friends.
Không. Mình đi bộ với bạn bè.
Did you do your science homework, Joan?
Bạn làm bài tập khoa học chưa, Joan?
No, I didn't. It was difficult. Did you do the science homework?
Chưa. Khó lắm. Bạn làm bài tập khoa học chưa?
Yes, I did. Let me help you.
Rồi. Để mình giúp bạn.